I’d like to dedicate this next song to Carmelo,
أريد أن أهدي هذه الأُغنية للكلب " كارميلوا "
who was put to sleep a couple of days ago, because he got too old.
والذي تم قتله منذ يومين لانه غدا طاعناً في السن
But apparently he was a very nice dog
وكلنه على ما يبدو كان كلباً لطيفاً جداً
and he always let the cat sleep in the dog bed.
فقد كان يدع دوما القطة في المنزل تنام في فراشه
♫ (Dog panting noise) Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh. ♫
♫ هيه , هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ♫
♫ I'm just a'walking my dog, singing my song, strolling along. ♫
♫ أنا فقط أتمشى مع كلبي الخاص , وأغني أُغنيتي وأتمشى على طول الطريق ♫
♫ Yeah, it's just me and my dog, catching some sun. We can't go wrong. ♫
♫ نعم .. إني فقط مع كلبي أتسمر قليلاً في الشمس .. ولن نصاب بأي مكروه ♫
♫ My life was lonely and blue. ♫
♫ لقد كانت حياتي وحيدة وزرقاء ♫
♫ Yeah, I was sad as a sailor, ♫
نعم ولقد كنت حزينة مثل البحار♫♫
♫ I was an angry 'un too. ♫
♫ كنت غاضبةً أيضاً ♫
♫ Then there was you -- appeared when I was entangled with youth and fear, ♫
♫ ثم ظهرت أنت - ظهرت عندما كنت مليئة بالخوف من شبابي - ♫
♫ and nerves jingle jangled, vermouth and beer were getting me mangled up. ♫
♫ وكانت أعصابي تمتلىء بالجنجل والخمر والبيرة وكان كان هذا يُفنيني ♫
♫ But then I looked in your eyes ♫
♫ ومن ثم نظرت إلى عينيك ♫
♫ and I was no more a failure. ♫
♫ ولم أعد أشعر في الفشل ♫
♫ You looked so wacky and wise. ♫
♫ فقد بدوت أحمقاً وذكياً ♫
♫ And I said, "Lord, I'm happy, 'cause I'm just a'walking my dog, ♫
♫ وقلت في نفسي " إلهي , أنا سعيدة لانني أتمشى مع كلبي ♫
♫ catching some sun. We can't go wrong." ♫
♫ أتسمر قليلاً في الشمس , ولن يصيبنا أي مكروه ♫
♫ Yeah, it's just me and my dog, singing our song, strolling along. ♫
♫ نعم أنه أنا وكلبي فحسب ,, نُغني أغنيتنا ,, ونتمشى على طول الطريق ♫
♫ 'Cause I don't care about your hating and your doubt, ♫
♫ لانني لم أعد أعبىء بكرهك لي وبشكك بي ♫
♫ and I don't care what the politicians spout. ♫
♫ ولم أعد أعبىء بما يقولوه السياسيون ♫
♫ If you need a companion, why, just go out to the pound, ♫
♫ وان اردت بعض التعاطف , ولماذا ؟ , فقط إذهب خارجاً إلى الفناء ♫
♫ and find yourself a hound, and make that doggie proud, ♫
♫ وجد لنفسك الولع الخاص بك وأجعل الكلب فخوراً بك ♫
♫ 'cause that's what it's all about. ♫
♫ لان هذا ما هو عليه الأمر ♫
♫ (Dog panting noise) Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh. ♫
♫ هيه , هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ♫
♫ My life was tragic and sad. ♫
♫ لقد كانت حياتي حزينة ومأساوية♫
♫ I was the archetypal loser. ♫
♫لقد كنت تلك الفاشلة التي يعرفها الجميع♫
♫ I was a pageant gone bad. ♫
♫لقد كنت فتاة حبلى أفسدت الامور♫
♫ And then there was you -- on time, and wagging your tail ♫
♫ومن ثم جئت انت بالوقت المناسب ,, تهز ذيلك ♫
♫ in the cutest mime that you was in jail. ♫
♫في اللحظة الألطف التي كنت بها في الأسر ♫
♫ I said, "Woof, be mine!" and you gave a wail and then ♫
♫قلت في نفسي " أيها الكلب كني مُلكي وقد نبحت ومن ثم ♫
♫ I was no longer alone. ♫
♫لم أعد وحيدة ♫
♫ And I was no more a boozer. ♫
♫ولم أعد ♫
♫ We'll make the happiest home. ♫
♫ وقد صنعنا البيت الأسعد♫
♫ And I said, "Lord, I'm happy, 'cause I’m just a'walking my dog, ♫
♫وقلت في نفسي " إلهي أنا سعيدة لانني أتمشى مع كلبي ♫
♫ singing my song, strolling along." ♫
♫أغني أغنيتي ,, و نسير على طول الطريق ♫
♫ Yeah, it's just me and my dog, catching some sun. We can't go wrong, ♫
♫ نعم أنه أنا وكلبي فحسب ,, نُغني أغنيتنا ,, ونتمشى على طول الطريق ♫
♫ 'cause I don't care about your hating and your doubt, ♫
♫ لانني لم أعد أعبىء بكرهك لي وبشكك بي ♫
♫ and I don’t care what the politicians spout. ♫
♫ ولم أعد أعبىء بما يقولوه السياسيون ♫
♫ If you need a companion, why, just go out to the pound, ♫
♫ وان اردت بعض التعاطف , ولماذا ؟ , فقط إذهب خارجاً إلى الفناء ♫
♫ and find yourself a hound, and make that doggie proud, ♫
♫ وجد لنفسك الولع الخاص بك وأجعل الكلب فخوراً بك ♫
♫ 'cause that's what it's all about, ♫
♫ لان هذا ما هو عليه الأمر ♫
♫ that's what it's all about, ♫
♫ هذا ما هو عليه الأمر ♫
♫ that's what it's all abou-BOW-WOW-WOW-WOW ♫
♫ لان هذا ما هو عليه الأمر - واو - واو - واو - واو ♫
♫ that's what it's all about. ♫
♫ لان هذا ما هو عليه الأمر ♫
♫ (Dog panting noise) Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh. ♫
♫ هيه , هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ,هيه ♫
Good dog!
كلب جيد !
Thank you.
شُكراً